imaging-resource.com 2019-06-15

# The Imaging Resource Privacy Policy

The Imaging Resource Privacy Policy

The Imaging Resource does not collect any user specific identifiable information other than what the user specifically volunteers. For example, this information may be volunteered when you register for the [forums](https://www.photo-forums.com/) or subscribe to the newsletter. We do not use this information for any purpose other than its intended use (to allow posting in the forums, to allow sending of the newsletter to a specific email address, etc.) We don't resell names or any individual data. We may report demographic information in the aggregate, but don't share information on individual readers. 

A possible exception to the above may occur when a company sponsors a sweepstakes or contest. In these cases the company is generally entitled to the raw data collected for the sweepstakes/survey.

The Imaging Resource collects some non user specific information such as the type of browser and operating system used. This information is used to assist us internally to provide the best site design and format for our users. We don't share any data that may be uniquely linked to any of our readers outside the IR organization.

Please note that third party ad servers may place and read cookies or use web beacons to collect information in your browser when you access third party ads served on our site. Please consult the Help documentation for your respective browser if you wish to disable such third party cookies.

Some network ads are served by Lijit Networks. For the information collected by this ad network, please see their privacy policy at:

Lijit Networks, Inc. Privacy Policy  
<https://www.lijit.com/company/privacy-policy>

Lijit collects only anonymous information unless you choose to submit personal information. Lijit permits readers to opt out of the collection of this anonymous site visit data. To opt out, please see the section labeled 'Opting Out' in the above privacy policy for additional information.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please send us a note. 

[Enter](http://www.dailydigitalphoto.com/potd-images/ir_potd_enter.htm) this month to win:

_1_ $300 Adorama Gift Certificate

_2_ $200 Adorama Gift Certificate

_3_ $100 Adorama Gift Certificate
